Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
5583/5
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
49.4 linear ft.
Records (documents), publications (documents).
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into three sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-52
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.
Subjects:
Industrial relations -- United States -- Sources.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records (documents); Publications (documents)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 3: Boxes 45-52
Related Collections:
5880: Archives Organization File V, Additional Company Documents
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- Nat'l. Wholesale Hardware Assoc. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Hardware Distribution: A Profile of Success, Publication (Box 23, Folder 1)
    By National Wholesale Hardware Association. Item is in English.
- National Women's Trade Union League, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Action Needed! Post-War Jobs for Women, Publication (Box 23, Folder 2)
    By National Women's Trade Union League. Item is in English.
- Navistar, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Health Line, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By NAVISTAR. Fall 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Intercom Vol. 3 Issue 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
    By NAVISTAR. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Inside NAVISTAR, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Legacy of Leadership: NAVISTAR, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: International from NAVISTAR: We Build transportation the trucks and services that move the nation, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Navistar reports a 53% increase in third quarter net earnings on 23 increase in sales, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: International 400-500 Series Medium Cabover, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: New DT 360 DTA 360 Premium Diesel Engines, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: S-Series Bus Chassis, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: International Tractors, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: 9300 Premium Conventional Set-Back Front Axle, Publication (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Nestle Company, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Nestle, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Nestle Company Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Report to Employees on 1980, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: It's Scholarship Time Again fo the Class of '82, Publication (Box 23, Folder 4)
    By Nestle Company Inc. January 31, 1981. Item is in English.
- Jersey Business & Industry Assoc., Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Letter from Bruce G. Coe, President, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By New Jersey Business & Industry Association. October 22, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Star Ledger, Publication (Box 23, Folder 5)
    By New Jersey Business & Industry Association. May 5, 1993. Item is in English.
- New United Motor Manufacturing, 1995; Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Standards of Conduct and Good Attendance, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
    By New United Motor Manufacturing. September 1995. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Standards of Conduct and Good Attendance, Publication (Box 23, Folder 6)
- New York Business Alliance. Phoenix House. Drugs Don't Work, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Drugs don't work: New York Business Alliance, Publication (Box 23, Folder 7)
    By New York Business Alliance Phoenix House. Item is in English.
- New York CLUW, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Proposed By-Laws, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
    By New York CLUW. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: NY CLUW Task Force on Model Contact Clauses, Publication (Box 23, Folder 8)
- New York City Office Of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: NYCCBL The First 25 Years, Publication (Box 23, Folder 9)
    By New York City Office of Collective Bargaining. Item is in English.
- New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Injured on the Job: A Handbook for NY Workers, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
    By New York Committee For Occupational Safety and Health. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Injured on the Job: A Guide to Workers' Compensation in New York State, Publication (Box 23, Folder 10)
- New York State, Dept. of Civil Service, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Instructor's Guide for Public Employee Training Courses, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    By New York State, Department of Civil Service. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Civil Service Extensions: Optional Forms Deadlines Functions, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Effective Civil Service: A Guide to the Administration of the Merit System in New York Municipalities, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Proposed Civil Service Rules for Cities, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
    By New York State, Department of Civil Service. August 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Seventy-Seventh Annual Report: New York State Department of Civil Service and Civil Service Commission, Publication (Box 23, Folder 11)
- New York State Department of Health - Training Together for Tots, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Training Together for Tots, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    By New York State Department of Health Training Together for Tots. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Training Together for Tots: Catalog of Early Intervention Workshops, Publication (Box 23, Folder 12)
    By New York State Department of Health Training Together for Tots. September 1997- January 1998. Item is in English.
- New York Jobs with Justice / Health Care Campaign, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Health Action: Newsletter, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
    By New York Jobs with Justice/ Health Care Campaign. February/ March 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Health Action: Newsletter, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
    By New York Jobs with Justice/ Health Care Campaign. August 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Health Action: Newsletter, Publication (Box 23, Folder 13)
- New York State Dept. of Labor, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: New York State Department Release: Unemployment Insurance Claims in New York State, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
    By New York State Department of Labor. August 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Unemployment Insurance Claims in New York State: August 1980, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
    By New York State Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Information Employers: Services Designed to Save you Time and Money!, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: Employment in Nonagricultural Establishments, By Place of Work New York State, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Item 5: Information for Employees, Publication (Box 23, Folder 14)
- New York Labor History Association, 1998; Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Labor History Month, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    By New York Labor History Association. May 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A Poster Map of the Most Important Events in Labor History from 1600 to present day, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    By New York Labor History Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: A Poster Map of the most important events in labor history from 1600 to present day, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: A Poster map of the most important events in labor history from 1600 to present-day, Publication (Box 23, Folder 15)
    By New York Labor History Association`. Item is in English.
- New York Law Journal, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: New York Law Journal: Corporate Counsel, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    By New York Law Journal. Feb. 4, 2002. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Outside Counsel Vol. 226 No. 107, Publication (Box 23, Folder 16)
    By Stephen E. Zweig and Nathan H. Williams. December 4, 2001. Item is in English.
- New York Personnel Management Assoc. - House Organs, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Recognition: The Key to Motivation and Productivity, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Productive Reading, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 22, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Recognition: The Key to Motivation and Productivity, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 12, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Bulletin Vol. 36 No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Bulletin Vol. 36 No. 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: NYPMA Vol. 36 No. 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Bulletin Vol. 36 No. 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. June 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Bulletin Vol. 36 No. 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. May 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Bulletin Vol. 37 No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. September 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Bulletin Vol. 37, No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Bulletin Vol. 37 No. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. November 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Bulletin Vol. 37 No. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. December 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Bulletin Vol. 37 No. 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. February 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Bulletin Bol. 37 No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Bulletin Vol. 37, No. 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Bulletin vol. 37 No. 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. June 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Bulletin Vol. 38 No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. September 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Bulletin Vol. 38 No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Bulletin Vol. 38 No. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. November 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Bulletin Vol. 38 No. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. December 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: The Corporate Trauma: Firing an Employee with Dignity, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 28, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Bulletin Vol. 38 No. 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Bulletin Vol. 38, No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Bulletin Vol. 38 No. 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. February 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Bulletin Vol. 37 No. 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1981. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Bulletin Vol. 38, No. 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Bulletin Vol. 38, No. 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. May 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Bulletin No. 38 No. 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. June 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Bulletin, Vol. 39, No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. September 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: New York Personnel Management Association, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. Bulletin Vol. 39 No. 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Bulletin Vol. 39 No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: Bulletin Vol. 39 no. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. November 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Bulletin Vol. 39 No. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. Januay 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Bulletin Vol. 39, No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. February 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Bulletin Vol. 39, No. 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Bulletin Vol. 39, No. 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Bulletin Vol. 39 No. 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. May 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Bulletin Vol. 39, No. 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. June 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: Bulletin Vol. 40, No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. September 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. November 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. December 1983. Item is in English.
  - Item 43: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 44: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. February 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 45: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Bulletin Vol. 40 No. 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. May 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 48: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. Septmber 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 49: Bulletin Vol. 40 no. 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. June 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 50: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 51: Bulletin Vol. 41 no. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. November 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 52: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Bulletin Vol. 41 no. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. December 1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 56: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. November 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 57: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 58: Bulletin Vol. 41 no. 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. February 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 59: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. May 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 60: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 11, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. September 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 61: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 10, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. June 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 62: Employment at Will: A Full Day Seminar Presented by NYPMA, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 63: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. December 1985. Item is in English.
  - Item 65: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 66: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 7, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 67: Bulletin Nol. 42 No. 6, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. Feb. 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 8, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. April 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: Bulletin Vol. 42 No. 9, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. May 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: Bulletin Vol. 43 No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1986. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: Bulletin Vol. 43 No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 72: Bulletin Vol. 43 No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: Bulletin Vol. 43 No. 2, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 74: Bulletin Vol. 43 No. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: Bulletin Vol. 44 No. 1, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. September 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: Bulletin, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. October 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 77: Bulletin, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 78: Bulletin Vol. 44 no. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. January 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 79: Bulletin Vol. 44, No. 3, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 80: Bulletin Vol. 44 No. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
    By New York Personnel Management Association. March 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 81: Bulletin Vol. 44 No. 4, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 82: Bulletin, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 83: Noted Author and Consultant to Discuss Entrepreneurship at June Meeting, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Item 84: Bulletin Vol. 41 No. 5, Publication (Box 23, Folder 17)
- New York Planning Council, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: National Defense and the Industrial Resources of New York State, Publication (Box 23, Folder 18)
    By New York Planning Council. Item is in English.
- New York State. Bureau of Workplace & Institutional Intervention Services, The and New York State Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse, Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Extending the Alcohol and Drug Free Workplace to Smaller Work Organizations: A Report on the Inventory of Employee Assistance Programs in New York State, Publication (Box 23, Folder 19)
    By New York State Bureau of Workplace & Institutional Intervention Services. November 1990. Item is in English.
- New York State. Department of Economic Development. Entrepreneurial Assistance Program, Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Entrepreneurial Assistance Program, Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
    By New York State Department of Economic Development, Entrepreneurial Assistance Program. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Entrepreneurial Assistance Program, Publication (Box 23, Folder 20)
- New York State. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: How to Prepare Yourself For Job Interviews, Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
    By New York State: Department of Labor. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Como Prepararse Para Una Entrevista de Trabajo, Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Guide to Preparing a Resume, Publication (Box 23, Folder 21)
- New York State. Department of Social Service, Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Myths Die Hard, Publication (Box 23, Folder 22)
    By New York State Department of Social Services. Jnuary 1985. Item is in English.
- New York State Public Employment Relations Board, Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Rules of Procedure: A Guide to the Taylor Law, Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
    By New York State Public Employment Relations Board. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: A New Initiative: Labor-Management Committees Under the Taylor law, Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Item 3: A Perb Initiative Labor-Management Committees Under the Taylor law, Publication (Box 23, Folder 23)
- New York State. Workers' Compensation Board, Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Injured on the job? An Employees' Guide to NYS Workers' Compensation Benefits, Publication (Box 23, Folder 24)
    By New York State Workers' Compensation Board. Item is in English.
- New York Shipping Association Inc. - Handbooks, manuals, etc., Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: NYSA to Present Awards for Safety, Publication (Box 23, Folder 25)